<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Team1Realty Real Estate Video Blog</title>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Team1Realty - your professional East Bay Area Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <link>http://tylg.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://tylg.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 16:25:12 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 16:25:12 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>What’s Our Market Doing This Fall?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/f-DHxQTRYsM&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 2016 market has seen quite a bit of change lately. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the spring, we started out red-hot with multiple offers on almost every property due to low inventory. We then saw a cool down during the summer, which confused a lot of sellers. &lt;strong&gt;Now in the fall, we’re seeing a stabilization&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some neighborhoods in some areas are still very hot for certain product types. Overall, though, we’re seeing low inventory in our area. The biggest change happening and the biggest concern for sellers is the fact that we’re seeing an increase in days on market. We’re seeing price reductions and price changes as well. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=We’re seeing low inventory and an increase in days on market.%20http://tylg.com/what-s-our-market-doing-this-fall.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“We’re seeing low inventory and an increase in days on market.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This means that, depending on whether you’d like to move up and where you’re moving, &lt;strong&gt;now may be a great time to sell&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or have a video topic in mind you’d like us to discuss, please feel free to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you! &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://tylg.com/what-s-our-market-doing-this-fall.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://tylg.com/what-s-our-market-doing-this-fall.html</guid>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Buyer Tips</category>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to My YouTube Channel</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/0XgjGsvd9S0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s my pleasure to welcome you to my new YouTube channel. Here you’ll find great seller tips, buyer tips, and plenty of market updates. If there’s a specific real estate topic you’d like to know more about, please let us know and we’ll make a video about it. We want to be a great real estate resource for you, so please feel free to take a look around in the meantime. We’ll talk to you soon!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://tylg.com/welcome-to-my-youtube-channel.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://tylg.com/welcome-to-my-youtube-channel.html</guid>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Buyer Tips</category>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
